[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Natalie] If you really want
to help Lily Cruz,
I can do whatever it is you want me to do.
And they'll listen.
Because I am their queen.
I think I'll be needing you,
sooner than later.
What do you mean Diego's missing?
What does Diego have to do with this?
First, Lily goes missing. Now, Diego too?
[Raul groaning]
Everyone has their secrets,
Raul. Deal with it!
[Julio] Your mother's probably
being raped right now!
[Lily] Your bastard!
When I get out of here,
I swear I will kill you!
[Helena] What?! Camia got away?!
Lily Cruz is getting away!
[Diego] Looking for this?!
[Damian] Go on.
Pull the damn trigger!
Watch as I command Lily Cruz to lay down!
[all laughing]
[Camia] You monsters!
Where's my daughter?!
Mom!
Lily!
[Helena speaks indistinctly]
[Helena] Hello, ladies.
I guess you already know
how you got yourselves into this.
You
tried to escape,
and you failed miserably!
[Helena laughing]
And it's all thanks
to my obedient soldiers.
And that dog collar you're
wearing around your neck, Lily.
We've got you where we want you.
And you ain't going nowhere!
Madam, there's been a new development.
There's been a new development?
-Come on!
[Diego] Come on!
Are you ready to die?!
Do it!
Diego. Uncle Damian.
[Helena] Time is running out.
Do you have any surprise for me?
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Shoot me!
[suspenseful music]
The hell I will!
But promise me you'll let Lily go!
Diego!
Don't!
Oh, sure. No problem.
[suspenseful music continues]
Shoot me!
[gunshot]
[Lily] No!
Finally!
Helena, you monster!
You bastards!
[tense music playing]
[Julio] They've finally decided.
[Helena] Finally.
[Helena laughs]
What?
[Julio] Well, well.
Lily!
-Those are the rules.
-Mm-hm.
Your mother dies.
No! No!
Goodbye, Camia.
No! No! No! Do you hear me?
I won't let you kill my mother!
You've reached a dead end.
Game over, Lily.
But my darling…
we're just starting.
-Darling, starting. It rhymes.
-[Helena laughs]
Papa.
What?
I want to see my daughter before I die.
Where is Lily?!
-[Camia] Lily!
-Mom, no! Mom!
Mom, no, you won't die.
You won't die, Mom!
Spare my mother!
[Lily] Please!
Just leave my mother alone, please!
Kill me instead! Let her go!
Take me! Kill me instead!
[melancholic music playing]
Lily!
[Lily] No!
No! Stop! Stop it!
Please, that's enough!
Mom!
Mom! No!
[tense music playing]
-Please don't hurt…
-Turn the sound off.
-my mother!
-I don't want them to hear this.
Papa, Lily Cruz has to die
before everything is over!
Turn it on. On. Hello! Mic test! Test!
Test mic! Can they hear me?!
Burn her!
Burn that witch!
Burn her! Come on. Burn! Burn! Burn!
[Helena] Romulo.
-Now.
-Burn!
[suspenseful music building]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[Emilia] Yeah. I love it.
-[mouths] Bye-bye.
-[Helena] Yes.
-Burn that witch!
-Yes!
Burn!
[muffled] Help!
[Lily groaning]
[Emilia] No!
-Turn it off. Turn it off.
-Wait. What are you doing?
Shut the hell up!
-I'm the one who kidnapped her!
-No!
So I get to decide what to do with her.
No. No!
No, no… No, not like this…
You know she can't die. It's too easy.
[Lily groaning]
[screams]
-Turn the audio back on.
-No.
Romulo!
Switch it off.
No, Julio!
No, Romulo!
This is my playground!
I call the shots here.
I'm in control here.
You're not in control here.
If you're going to burn me alive…
…then just spare my mother, please!
[Lily groaning]
[Helena laughing]
Oh, my, Lily!
Do I have to smash my crown in your face
just to remind you who the real queen is?!
[Helena] Huh?
First, I'll kill your mother.
Then, I'll kill you!
No!
Romulo, turn up the incinerator!
Romulo, now!
-Go! Burn her!
-Yes!
-No! No!
-I said no!
Grandpa! I said, stop this!
-Mama…
-No! No!
-Romulo…
-No!
Turn the audio back on!
-I'm talking to Ro--
Romulo, I said…
…stop it!
[screaming]
[breathing raggedly]
No, Julio!
You, Helena, are not the only
player in this playground.
Remember,
we are a family.
And we must all agree
on one final decision.
Well?
Are you still alive?
[tense music playing]
Come on, Red Dragon!
-What more do you want?!
-[gunshots]
Where's Lily?!
Bravo.
Took you long enough, but good job.
Where's Lily?!
I played your game. I killed Damian!
Now bring Lily to me,
just as you promised!
If you think she's still alive,
then go look for her.
I just want you to know…
that you will never see
Lily Cruz alive again.
-You think you're tough?
-[Diego groans]
What the hell was that?!
I was trying to be fair.
[scoffs] Fair? Fair to whom, huh?
Fair to Lily or fair to your ego?
Didn't you hear what Arnaldo said?
I don't want him to be part of this.
You know what I mean.
If you wanna be my partner,
you have to learn to compromise.
Helena, my dear perfect partner,
that's not true.
You want to know the truth, huh?
I have a long, long list of ways
to make an enemy suffer.
She doesn't need your fire.
You know what we'll do?
I'll bash her head in
until my hands give in.
I mean…
I mean our hands. Sorry.
Slip of the tongue. Our hands.
And then…
we will mess with her brain
until she can no longer tell
what's right from wrong.
We will drive her insane,
as she did my grandson.
And then what?
And then we will be laughing
our heads off.
Because we Ardientes
always get the last laugh.
[laughing maniacally]
You see? You see?
[Julio sighs]
You know, I should've been practicing
my eulogy for Lily Cruz.
But she's still alive because of you.
She should've been burnt
to a crisp right now.
Grandpa has made up his mind.
We can't do anything about it.
You know he did that all for you.
Well, my grandma is on your side.
Because Papa…
He keeps drilling these silly ideas
into Mama's brain,
like torturing Lily Cruz
first before killing her.
Can't you guys see, huh?
If she dies, we're all gonna be happy now!
I was there, remember?
I was her first victim.
I was her first target.
I will never forget the hell
she made me go through.
And now my memories are back,
and I'm reminded once again
of every single thing she put me through.
I still see and feel everything.
[melancholic music playing]
[Arnaldo] Give me one
good reason to trust you.
Arnaldo…
I love you.
And this…
this is your prize.
Ivy Aguas…
will you marry me?
Yes.
Yes, Arnaldo, I will marry you.
Yes!
Diego is just a friend.
Because I'm all yours, Arnaldo.
I love you so much,
that's why I'm marrying you.
[priest] Do you, Ivy,
take Arnaldo to be
your lawfully wedded husband?
Stop the wedding!
-No, no!
-I don't love you! I don't love you!
I'll never love a monster like you! Never!
I never loved you, and I never will!
You're right, I love her.
But I'd also love to see her beg.
She made a complete fool of me.
For that, I wanna see her crawl
at my feet and beg for her life!
I want her to be my slave.
But you, on the other hand,
I understand…
you're just burdened by
your loyalty to Grandma.
But me, you, and Grandpa…
we share the same blood.
We all want the same thing.
And that is to destroy Lily Cruz
and make her beg for mercy.
[phone chimes]
I have to go.
Where are you off to?
Arnaldo, where are you going?
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
Who disposed of Damian's body?
Boss, Ramirez and Salazar did.
Ramirez and Salazar? Okay.
Boss, what should we do with him?
Let's just kill him
before he tries to escape.
Hold your horses.
We need to wait for our bosses' orders.
We'll get to that eventually.
Just keep an eye on him,
and don't let him get away.
Understood? I'll call the Governor.
[grunting]
Let me out of here!
You soulless criminals!
-Shut up! [grunts]
-[Lily groaning]
[Lily groans]
Shut your damn mouth!
[breathes heavily]
Damn you. Damn you all.
Damn you.
[ominous music playing]
Where is your son going?
I don't know, Mama.
Sometimes, as a mother, it's
so hard for me to sort him out.
It's Papa's fault.
He spoiled Arnaldo rotten.
Your Papa has single-handedly
ruined everybody else's life
here in this town.
Mama, what are you doing here,
just standing here?
You can't let him control everything.
[sighs] I need a breather.
An hour with Julio is like a year in hell!
But be careful, Mama.
You know that he won't think
twice about double-crossing you.
Yes. I'm aware of that.
And I've learned from my mistakes.
I will never forget the hell
that he all put us through.
He will never hurt us again.
[tense music building]
Julio?
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[doctor] There's been a problem.
-But I promise…
-My baby!
…we will do everything to save your baby.
[Helena] My baby! They're taking my baby!
Can't you hear her crying?
My baby! Doc! Doc!
[melancholic music]
When Julio took you away from me,
he also took away my reason for living.
I was so angry that it almost killed me!
But on that day,
the Red Dragon was born.
The most fierce syndicate head
of our country.
[sighs] Do you think
I would still have turned out this way
if Julio hadn't stolen you from me?
Before he took you from me,
all I wanted was to be a good mother.
For us to have a simple and quiet life.
Why are you saying these things, Mama?
Are you starting to have regrets?
I took everything that life threw at me.
I could have easily chosen
to forgive, to heal,
to bury my anger.
But instead, I embraced that anger,
and it's made me who I am today.
If given a chance…
I wouldn't change a thing.
Because in the end…
I found you, Emilia.
After all these years.
And I will never let you go again.
I won't allow anyone…
to ruin our lives again.
Not that Lily Cruz!
And certainly,
not Julio Ardiente.
-I love you so much.
-I love you.
Damn you.
Damn you all.
[sighs]
[Diego] What if something happens
tomorrow or the day after?
What if we don't get our
happily ever after?
Diego, don't say that.
Lily, we can't know for sure.
You know that.
We don't know what the future holds.
But we have tonight.
Lily Cruz, will you marry me?
Yes, Diego.
I will marry you.
[Camia] Lily!
Mom!
Lily!
-Diego!
-[Camia] Lily!
I will get you.
I will kill you all.
[suspenseful music building]
[suspenseful music playing]
I will find you
and your mother, Lily.
I won't give up until I get you
away from the Ardientes.
Anna. Anna, wait up.
I'm sorry for what I said.
And… you're right.
We need to work together
in order to find Lily and Diego.
Thank you, Marlon.
[Arnaldo] Anna?
Arnaldo, what are you doing here?
I heard about what happened to Lily.
Do you know anything?
I'm not sure because I haven't
seen Grandpa, Mama, and Grandma.
What?
Do you think they kidnapped
Auntie Camia and Lily?
I have no doubt
that the Ardientes are behind it.
You can't trust that man, Anna.
He's an Ardiente too.
[Marlon] Come on, Mister Danny.
We all know Arnaldo's changed.
[Danny] Fine.
If you really are a changed man,
then go look for Lily and the Ardientes.
If you don't, we'll just have to
scour the forest ourselves.
Because we heard that's
where they were last seen.
It's dangerous, what you're planning.
Please don't go unarmed.
It's risky out there.
But I'll call Mama.
It's the least I can do to help.
[Marlon] Calm down.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ah, as usual, Mama isn't picking up.
But don't worry.
I will find Lily
and that bastard who took her.
I promise you, I'll bring her back.
[metal clanking]
Mom.
[action music playing]
Mom. I'll save you.
I'm coming, Mom.
I'll save you.
[action music playing]
[tense music playing]
Mom?
Mom.
-Mom!
-Lily.
[suspenseful music]
Mom.
-Lily.
-Mom.
Mom.
Mom, are you okay? Did they hurt you?
I promise you, Mom.
I'll do all I can.
We'll get out of here. I'll save you, Mom.
How, Lily?
Will we ever get out of here?
How will we even escape?
How, Lily?
Mom.
[dramatic music]
Mom?
Mom!
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Mom?
[somber music building]
Mom, can you hear me?
Mom?
Mom!
Lily!
Mom! Just talk to me, please!
I can hear you!
Lily!
I'm here, Mom.
I'm on the other side.
Mom?
Mom, are you okay? Mom?
Mom, did they hurt you?
Did they give you something to eat?
No, Lily.
How about you?
Are you sure you're okay?
I haven't lost hope, Mom.
I promise I will save you, Mom.
Did you hear that?
I'll save you!
I trust you, Lily.
I know we can make it out of here.
Lily…
if this were all a dream,
I'd be the one to save you.
But that's just not how it is.
There are cameras watching us
every second of the day.
Lily…
How? Will we ever see each other again?
Yes, we will, Mom!
I have a plan.
Ah.
I still don't understand
why you're so happy
with what we're doing.
We are wasting our time.
Helena.
They say that time you enjoy wasting…
is not wasted time.
And besides,
I'm sure you'll
find all this entertaining.
Ugh!
Another one of your clichés.
Mom, I know they can hear us,
but I don't care!
I don't give a damn anymore!
[tense music playing]
-[metal clanking]
-[Lily groaning]
Ardientes!
I know you can hear me!
And what is she doing, Papa?
She's losing it.
-She's going crazy.
-Hey, that's not nice.
[Julio and Arnaldo laughing]
Sorry, my son.
-[Lily continues groaning]
-[metal clanking]
[Camia] Lily. Don't.
Lily!
[Lily groaning]
[Lily] Well?!
-[metal clanking]
-[Lily groaning]
Come and get me, you bastards!
[Lily continues groaning]
Ardientes!
Can you hear me?!
I know you're watching me!
-Yeah.
-[Lily groaning]
Well?! Show yourselves!
Come out and face me, you cowards!
I love challenges like this.
-[Lily groaning]
-[Julio clears throat]
Romulo.
[Lily] Well?!
-[Lily continues groaning]
-[metal clanking]
[Lily groaning]
[tense music playing]
[groans]
-[man 1] Boss.
-[man 2] Boss.
Ramirez and Salazar should be here by now.
Where are they?
They probably went off
to their girlfriends.
Don't start with me.
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
[Magbanua] Oh.
[laughs]
Our guest is finally awake.
What's up?
Listen, I have good news.
Our bosses have already
given us the go signal.
We're getting rid of him now.
Okay, boys.
[man 3] Finally.
Who wants to go first?
[suspenseful music playing]
Any last words?
[door opens]
[action music playing]
[rapid gunfire]
[Diego and Magbanua groaning]
[action music continues playing]
Listen to me. We don't have
to kill each other.
If we work together, we can get
Auntie Camia and Lily back.
Here's the plan.
I'll shoot, but the bullet
will only graze you.
-Shoot me!
-[gunshot]
[Diego] You need to convince
them that you actually died.
We're going to turn the tables on them.
Start digging, man.
Hey, he still has a pulse.
Finish him off.
[action music playing]
-[man groaning]
-[gunshot]
-[man 2 groans]
[action music continues playing]
Where are Lily and Camia?
[Diego] Now!
Tell me where they are!
[Damian] You're a tough one to crack.
Tell us where the Ardientes
took Lily and Camia!
[chuckling]
You tell me where they are right now!
[groans]
[Magbanua groaning]
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
They only asked me to guard you.
I have no idea where Lily and Camia are.
Don't lie to us!
I don't know.
[emphatic] I don't know.
[chuckles]
Show your ugly faces!
Come and get me, Ardientes!
[grunting]
-Lily, what are you doing?
-Come on!
Lily!
Come out wherever you are!
[grunts]
[Lily screaming]
[groaning]
Not so tough now, are we?
I thought you had a surprise
for when I got back.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
Uh… Grandpa.
Yeah?
I think you should check this out.
[Julio] Ooh. Yeah.
This I got to see.
Why don't you come closer?
[suspenseful music]
[Romulo groaning]
What the--
[groans]
Lily. What's going on?
[suspenseful music continues]
[Romulo groans, coughs]
[Romulo groans]
[Romulo groaning]
Hey, Papa, what just happened?
You have to send backup.
Do something!
Will you please stop panicking?
[tense music swelling]
[Julio] Damn you!
[screams]
[electricity buzzing]
[Lily groans]
[Julio laughs]
[Romulo grunting]
[grunts]
[electricity buzzing]
[Romulo groaning]
What?!
[object clatters]
Damn you!
[tense music playing]
Lily, I'm here!
Lily!
Mom?
Lily.
[Camia] Lily!
Mom?
[unsettling music playing]
[action music playing]
[gunfire]
[gunshot]
[action music continues]
Mom?
Lily, I'm here!
Lily.
Mom!
Mom?
-Mom?
-Lily!
[Camia shouting] Lily!
Lily!
Mom?
Mom!
Lily, I'm here!
Lily!
[tense music playing]
Where's my daughter?
Lily is coming back for me,
so you better watch out!
What makes you think your daughter's here?
[Lily screams]
-Where's my mother?!
-[gunshot]
Lily.
[gunshots]
[tense music continues]
Where is she?!
-Lily Cruz!
-[gunfire]
[Helena] What are we gonna do?!
We're about to lose!
Are you enjoying the show, Ardientes?
Once I get out of here,
I'll give you a good reason
to be scared for your lives!
-[Julio] What's this?
-That's impossible.
Damian is dead.
I saw Diego kill Damian myself.
What the hell is Jaguar doing there?
Those damn Cruzes will
never die, will they?!
[Emilia] Damn you, Jaguar!
I'm going to kill you!
[Lily] Mom. I'm here.
[theme music playing]